[ RUSTLING ]
[ IN ENGLISH ] Mr. Kim .
I hate dust more than anything .
[ IN ENGLISH ] I 'll - - I 'll clean it again .
You don 't have to clean up now .
Why don 't you dump this first ?
That 's formalin .
Formaldehyde , to be precise .
To be even more precise , dirty formaldehyde .
Every bottle is coated with layers of dust .
Pour ' em into the sink .
Ex - - Excuse me ?
Just empty every bottle to the very last drop .
It 's just - - They are toxic chemicals ,
and the regulations states that - -
Pour them right down the drain , Mr. Kim .
If I pour them in the drain ,
they will run into the Han River .
That 's right .
Let 's just dump them in the Han River .
But , you know , this is not just any toxic chemicals - -
The Han River is very ... broad , Mr. Kim .
Let 's try to be broad-minded about this .
Hm ?
Anyway ,
that 's an order .
So ...
start pouring .
[ LIQUID BURBLING ]
[ ♪ ]
[ IN KOREAN ] What the heck is this ?
[ IN KOREAN ] What ?
That 's pretty gross .
Is it a mutation ?
[ CHUCKLES ]
Is it dead ?
No , it moved a second ago .
Yeah ? Wait ...
[ WATER ROARING ]
My cup !
That was close .
My daughter gave me this cup .
Look , it 's swimming away .
MAN 1 : How many tails does that thing have ?
MAN 2 : You got me . Makes your skin crawl .
[ IN KOREAN ] Mr. Yoon !
What the hell are you doing ?
Don 't do it !
No ! No !
[ IN KOREAN ] Did you guys see that ?
Underneath ...
In the water .
Something dark in the water .
You really didn 't see it ?
What the hell are you talking about ?
Morons , to the very end .
Have a good life .
[ ♪ ]
[ IN KOREAN ] Welcome .
What would you like ?
[ IN KOREAN ] How much is this ?
Seventy-five cents .
Ah ! Not again .
Lift your head .
One , two , three . Here you are .
WOMAN [ IN KOREAN ] : Daddy !
[ IN KOREAN ] Hyun-seo ?
Hyun-seo .
Wait for me !
Now that you 're awake ,
get up !
Three squids for Mat 4 . Roast them quickly .
Gosh , how much sleep can a body take ?
Hyun-seo !
Here you are .
Ugh ! Oh .
Oh , that hurts .
Did your uncle do a good job ?
[ IN KOREAN ] He came , at least .
I was worried .
I can 't believe this .
I was the only one whose uncle came to parents ' day .
That 's why I kept calling , but you didn 't answer .
Why didn 't you answer ?
You think this phone can receive signals ?
I am too embarrassed to use it in public .
You take it .
What 's wrong with it ?
Oh , and about uncle .
I could smell alcohol on him
when he stood in the back of class .
That punk ,
getting drunk at this hour .
Hasn 't it started , Grandpa ?
What ?
Today 's Nam-joo 's competition .
Aren 't we gonna watch ?
Oh , Nam-joo !
Right .
[ MUSIC PLAYING OVER TV ]
Why isn 't it on ?
You know what this is ?
What ?
I 'm saving up to get you a new phone .
There 's a lot , huh ?
[ COINS RATTLING ]
They 're all dimes !
That 'll never be enough .
There are some quarters too .
What 's this penny doing here ?
This is all from the change box , huh ?
I 'll tell Grandpa .
Go ahead . Tell the geezer .
Geezer ?
It 's a dead body .
WOMAN [ ON TV ] : Mr. Yoon 's body
without the lower half ... HYUN-SEO : That 's gross .
... was discovered from Han River .
Turn to 505 . The sports channel .
Oh , there it is ! I made that for her . Aunt !
A bull 's-eye every time ! Park Nam-joo !
Grandpa !
The old man has to run the shop ,
let 's watch it ourselves .
What do you mean ? We all need to support her .
HYUN-SEO : Grandpa !
Let the geezer roast some squid .
GANG-DU : A straw .
Let 's have a cold one .
Here .
This is alcohol !
You 're in middle school now .
What ? Are you really my father ?
When your daddy was in middle ...
All right ! The semi-finals !
Wow . She looks tough .
Mm !
It 's bitter !
Go , Park Nam-joo !
Who else could take so long to take a shot ?
Oh , it started .
Nam-joo is on . You gonna watch ?
Gold medal time !
GRANDPA : I can 't watch my daughter 's matches .
Gold medal this time !
Gang-du .
Yeah ? Come outside .
I have to watch this .
Come on out .
Now !
I received ...
a complaint from Mat 4 .
Their squid had only nine legs .
Did you eat one ?
No .
Don 't deny it !
Why touch other people 's things ?
Think of it from the customer 's perspective .
A squid .
The torso tastes delicious , but the legs ,
especially the longest one , has something special , right ?
From a paying customer 's perspective ,
it 's important .
Take this to Mat 4 .
Tell them it 's on the house .
Four , five , six , seven , eight , nine , 10 .
Mat 4 .
I 've brought your order .
Oh , put it down there .
What are you looking at ?
There 's something there . Come on .
There , under the bridge .
See it ?
Do you see it ?
How long has it been there ?
It 's been a while .
I told you .
Ah , it 's construction equipment .
Something they hung ? No .
Don 't think so . It 's moving .
MAN 1 : Yeah , it just moved .
MAN 2 : Did it ?
[ SCREAMING ]
GRANDPA : Bull 's-eye !
She 's amazing !
I 'm not just saying that because she 's my daughter .
How could she hit the exact center like that ?
Right !
HYUN-SEO : I can 't believe it !
Let 's close the stand today .
[ CROWD MURMURING AND GASPING ]
MAN 1 : It 's going in .
MAN 2 : It 's swimming over !
[ CHATTERING ]
God , it 's huge .
[ PHONE BEEPING ]
ALL : Ooh !
Did you see that ? He ate the can !
All in one gulp .
Is it a dolphin ?
Yeah , must be .
Have some beer nuts too !
MAN 3 : Should we throw something too ?
MAN 4 : Pakistan ? You came from Pakistan ?
MAN 5 : It swam off .
MAN 6 : It 's gone now .
MAN 7 : It 's an Amazonian river dolphin for sure .
[ CHATTERING EXCITEDLY ]
This time there are ten legs , Mister .
This time there are ten legs . Count them yourself .
[ ♪ ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ CREATURE ROARING ]
Ahh !
Run away ! Everyone run away !
Run away !
[ MAN SINGING OVER HEADPHONES ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ♪ ]
[ WOMAN TALKING OVER SPEAKERS ]
[ MUFFLED SCREAMING , SHOUTING ]
Open up !
[ RUMBLING ]
WOMAN : Young-ho !
Young-ho ! My son must be in there .
Someone help , please !
[ IN ENGLISH ] What are you doing ?
There 's people in there . I gotta go help .
[ IN KOREAN ] Help !
[ IN ENGLISH ] Donald , don 't go !
Come on , Donald . Come back !
You 're gonna get hurt !
[ IN ENGLISH ] Hey , hey , hey , hey ! Let me help ! Let me help !
Hey , man ! You 're not gonna get this door open .
[ IN KOREAN ] Okay .
[ YELLING ]
Hey !
[ MONSTER GRUNTS ]
[ STAMMERING ]
WOMAN [ IN ENGLISH ] : Donald ! Where are you going ?
Donald ! Come back !
Donald ! Donald ! Listen to me !
Get it up ! Get it up !
Faster ! Let 's go !
Throw it hard !
WOMAN : Donald !
[ GROWLING ]
[ WOMAN SCREAMING LOUDLY ]
Ugh !
[ YELLING ]
[ SCREECHING ]
MAN [ IN KOREAN , OVER TV ] : This is the last shot of the semi-finals .
Ooh , now is not the time to lower her bow .
Shoot !
Because if she goes over the clock ...
GRANDPA : Shoot !
Two , one ...
[ CLOCK BUZZES ]
Oh , no ! The clock !
You could have just let go .
Park 's weakness is ...
Why can 't she let go sooner ?
... taking too long to release .
And today it cost her the title .
At this point , Park can only hope for the bronze .
[ CAN FIZZING ]
[ SCREAMING IN DISTANCE ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ♪ ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
[ LOUD SPLASH ]
[ CROWD CHATTERING INDISTICTLY ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ ♪ ]
[ CROWD SCREAMING ]
Hyun-seo !
MAN : Hey , come back !
Gang-du !
Hyun-seo !
GRANDPA : Hyun-seo !
GANG-DU : Hyun-seo !
Hyun-seo !
MAN : Sir !
[ KNOCKING ]
Sir !
You have ten minutes to clear the area !
Please take care of your things and evacuate .
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
GRANDPA : Come on .
[ CHATTERING , SOBBING ]
Nam-joo .
GANG-DU : Hyun-seo !
It 's bronze . Bronze .
Your aunt ...
brought you a bronze medal .
[ SOBBING ]
Hyun-seo .
It 's your aunt .
[ WAILING , SOBBING ]
GANG-DU : Hyun-seo .
Hyun-seo , your uncle came .
Hyun-seo !
Thanks to you , we 're all together !
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
Let go of me !
What are you taking pictures of ?
What 's so goddamn interesting ? Fuck off !
Stop taking pictures !
MAN : Calling the owner of a Hyundai car ,
plate number 2487 !
The plate number 2487 !
Anyone ?
Hey lady , how could you park your car there ?
So you screwed up ? I heard everything .
You grabbed some other girl 's hand ?
You left Hyun-seo on the ground ?
Your own daughter !
You call yourself a fucking father ?
You son of a bitch !
[ YELLING AND SHRIEKING ]
I thought it was Hyun-seo 's hand !
[ FAMILY SHOUTING AND WAILING ]
She 's so pretty in that photo .
She looks just like
her mom in that photo .
Do you think her mom even knows
that she died ?
Not a chance .
It 's been 13 years since she popped out the baby
and ran off .
I 'd run away too , damn it .
[ SNORING ]
Are you sleeping ?
Huh ?
GRANDPA : Nam-il .
You can sleep at a time like this ?
GRANDPA : What are you doing to your brother ?
In a word ...
Her birth was an accident ,
and so was her death .
Old people have always said
that an animal which kills a human
should be torn limb from limb .
That it 's a human 's duty to do so .
Until I slit that beast 's stomach and ...
At least find Hyun-seo 's body ,
I 'll never leave this world in peace .
Attention , please !
Ladies and gentlemen ,
those of you present at the river incident ,
there are probably a lot of you here .
This is an important matter of life and death .
Those who were at the scene
or those who have come in contact with these people ,
raise your hands !
This isn 't something you should hide .
Raise your hands .
If you go home , it might affect your families .
Raise ' em high !
Hey , mister .
What the hell is going on here ?
Fuck , shouldn 't you start by explaining what 's happening ?
ALL : Yeah , explain !
An explanation should be appearing on the TV news now .
To save time , we 'll let the news serve as explanation .
Okay , the news ...
The news ...
isn 't on now .
Shit .
Anyway ,
from this moment ,
you fall under our control ,
so start moving !
This is for your own safety .
[ SCREAMING AND INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ]
We have transport buses waiting outside now .
Okay , please move toward the buses
in an orderly fashion .
That 's right .
Watch your children .
Oh , did anyone here touch or come into direct contact
with the creature ?
Um ...
I didn 't touch it .
But some of its blood got sprayed in my face .
Don 't move ! Tell him to freeze !
Grab him ! Grab that one !
Please remain calm , people .
GRANDPA : What are you doing ?
My son didn 't touch anything !
MAN : Let 's go !
GRANDPA : Gang-du ! Get out of there !
GANG-DU : Dad !
GRANDPA : Gang-du ! Don 't go !
Gang-du , don 't worry . I 'm coming with you .
Stop there ! Hey , number 31 ! Stop !
MAN [ OVER SPEAKERS ] : This is a news flash .
It now appears that the creature ,
which disappeared after its attack
on surprised park-goers today ,
is far more dangerous than previously assumed .
U.S. Army Sergeant Donald White ,
who fought bravely with the creature
and lost an arm in the process ,
is now undergoing treatment at a U.S. Army hospital .
After a thorough examination ,
U.S. Army medical staff have identified
an unknown virus , primarily in body parts
that came into contact with the creature .
[ IN ENGLISH ] I can 't give any of that information
without the approval of the United States .
ANNOUNCER [ IN KOREAN ] : The U.S. Army has shipped a sample of the virus
to the U.S. Center for Disease Control ,
which confirmed that the creature from the Han River ,
as with the Chinese civet wildcat and SARS ,
is the host of this deadly new virus .
All military units sent to pursue
and capture the creature
have been recalled due to the risk of infection .
Only special forces trained in biological warfare
and disinfectant units are allowed access
to the Han River area .
Damn ,
they made a fuss dragging us in here !
What is this shit ?
Where are all the guys in yellow ?
Look !
The doctors aren 't even wearing masks .
Hello , sir !
When might we be allowed to go home ?
You can 't go home .
What ? We can 't ?
Dad , am I dying ?
Don 't say that !
Just do what the doctors tell you .
But , Dad , my back feels itchy and weird .
Like something 's moving .
It 's a squirmy feeling , like something 's there .
It 's because you never take a bath , it 's okay .
WOMAN : Attention ! Numbers 25-40 , raise your hands . Quickly !
This group , move to Room 904 now .
MAN 1 : Not again !
MAN 2 : That 's not us .
Don 't tell anyone about the blood on your face , okay ?
Mr. Park Gang-du ?
Yes ?
You need to take a lot of tests ,
so don 't eat until tomorrow morning .
What ? Don 't eat anything ?
Don 't feed him anything . No food .
[ SNORES LIGHTLY ]
[ ♪ ]
[ LOUD VIBRATION ]
Hello ?
GIRL : Hello ?
Can you hear me ?
My battery is ... Hello ?
It 's me , Hyun-seo !
Dad , can you hear me ? Please answer me !
Is this Hyun-seo ?
Dad , listen to me ! I can 't get out !
You 're alive ? Where ?
It 's like a big sewer . Really big and deep .
Where ?
Hello ?
I 'm scared !
Come quick !
Is it Hyun-seo ?
What is it ?
Did you see that ?
What ?
Wait a minute .
Sweet !
Hey !
Hey , don 't go near the water .
Be careful .
Let 's go . I 'm starving .
It 's okay , get back in .
[ ROARS ]
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
[ ♪ ]
[ CHOKING ]
Mister .
Mister !
Try to turn ...
[ CHOKING ]
[ GASPS ]
MAN : Your daughter , Park Hyun-seo ,
a seventh grader at Dangsan Middle School .
She 's on the deceased list .
Yes , she goes to Dangsan School .
She 's deceased ,
but she 's not dead .
I mean , she died , but she 's still alive .
Now you 're talking in circles .
So she 's on the list .
Wait , shut up .
At any rate , there was a call .
Right .
So shouldn 't you be able
to trace the call or something ?
Trace the call ?
That 's not something we do for just anyone .
Are you even aware of how complicated that is ?
" Just anyone , " is that what you said ?
Stop it .
Step back .
Please , officer , let 's talk like reasonable people .
They 're just kids , don 't ...
What are you doing ?
Your daughter never called you in the first place , okay ?
Your son had a dream ,
but it was so real that - -
You don 't believe anything we said ?
Now you 're obstructing an officer in the line of duty
Step back , Nam-joo .
Officer , should I explain it again ?
The way it happened was - -
I know .
I know . You yourself saw your daughter die .
But she called you in the middle of the night ?
Does that make any sense ?
That 's completely ridiculous !
A servant of the people , talking back like that ?
Then what 's your problem ? You fucking - -
Stop !
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
This is ...
This is my daughter ,
Park Hyun-seo .
My daughter ...
I 'm the creature .
I ate her . Okay ?
And then ...
It happened like this . This is a sewer .
You don 't understand ?
He 's received psychological treatment ?
He 's not a bad man ,
but he 's in shock .
We should understand .
Officer !
My daughter is alive in the sewer . Officer ?
Cut it out !
Your putting on a damn show doesn 't help !
My friend 's nephew 's husband 's
brother-in-law is a cop , maybe we should contact him ?
Right , I 'm sure he 'd bend over backwards for us .
You 're a college graduate , can 't you even persuade a cop ?
What 's college got to do with it ?
I put you through school selling cup ramen , and you - -
Dad .
Huh ?
How long 's it been since she 's eaten ?
Down in the sewer ?
What 's there to eat down there ?
You over there .
Hey , blondie , stop !
Run !
Out of the way !
Catch them !
[ SCREAMING , SHOUTING ]
Out of the way ! Quick !
This way !
Gang-du , hurry up !
Which floor ?
Close the door ! Quick !
I 'm coming down , but I 'm in the elevator so - -
Where is he ?
B4 A3 !
What did I just say ?
BOTH : B4 A3 !
[ ♪ ]
A3 . Where is A3 ?
A3 . There it is !
Stop ! Catch that car .
[ SHOUTING ]
MAN : Stop them !
Hurry ! Open the door !
Hurry !
Go ! Step on it !
Hurry up ! Nam-joo !
Where is Nam-joo ?
Did they catch her ? Oh , shit !
Where ?
There , there !
Over there . That idiot !
How could you leave your only sister ?
We can pick her up !
GRANDPA : Pick her up then !
She 's always been slow .
Mister , can you stop here ?
Hurry up !
What a dimwit ! Hurry it up , will you ?
Quick ! Quick !
Hey , family ! Everyone stop . Stop the van .
Hey , stop !
[ ♪ ]
Did we make it ?
That does it .
MAN : This won 't do .
The basic fee for pickup and the items you ordered is
7,500 bucks .
Including the Han River sewer map .
Plus ,
we brushed off a cop in the parking lot ,
and two police cars on the road .
Anyway ,
including hazard fees ,
the total is $ 11,400 .
Wow , Gang-du on TV .
That 's my citizen ID photo .
It 's from one of those subway photo booths ?
Hey , we should tape this
and show it to Hyun-seo . Daddy on TV .
Jesus .
We don 't accept these .
If you 're short on cash , we accept cards .
[ LAUGHS ]
We 'll just take the card .
WOMAN [ DISTORTED VOICE , ON TV ] : The blonde one ,
who made direct contact with it .
He 's the stupidest of all .
That bitch ! Listen to the mouth of her .
He pounced on me and slammed me to the floor .
I think he gave me arthritis . I 'll need treatment , I 'm sure .
That 's what he 's like .
GANG-DU : I know who she is .
Like we can 't recognize her through that voice disguiser ?
But they keep reporting on us .
In addition , the daughter among the escaped family members
is confirmed to be Park Nam-joo ,
national bronze medalist in archery .
What the hell ? How come there 's nothing about me ?
There 's nothing special about you .
Plenty of unemployed university grads these days .
I sacrificed my youth
for the democratization of our country ,
and those fuckers won 't even give me a job .
The passwords are all 1234 ?
There 's a white van outside .
It 's a disinfection truck , you can take it .
... expressed concern that Korea is
not adequately quarantining the infected . The U.S. also ...
Come on , let 's go .
GANG-DU : That 's the truck ?
Does it really work ?
This is what you got after spending all your assets ?
This gun is ...
Fuck , we 're not boy scouts .
And why only two disinfectant suits ?
So two of us should just creep around hiding ?
Dad , shouldn 't this be yellow ?
If it 's not yellow , they 're bound to catch us .
Well , let 's think of it as a different team .
Wow , this map is the topping on the cake .
The red circles indicate sewers ?
You spent $ 500 on this ? Really ?
But ...
I got it from a civil servant who knows the sewer system .
It 's photocopied on the back of used paper .
Hey , a guard post . Get down !
NAM-IL : Cover up , quickly !
Your blonde hair is showing .
GRANDPA : Get down quickly !
Whatever , you two handle it .
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
[ ♪ ]
What ? If that 's their attitude , why even bother ?
Bunch of lazy bums .
GRANDPA : Quiet ! Stop .
Mr. Park ?
Mr. Bacteria ?
Lower your mask .
This definitely a Daesung disinfectant truck .
But are you Daesung people ?
Yes , but we 're ...
a different team .
Oh , really ?
I 'm Manager Cho from the district office .
Don 't you know who I am ?
You know that 14 different companies
are doing the fumigation on shifts ?
But Daesung just barged in at the end .
To the other companies , it seems odd .
So I spoke with President Kwak yesterday ...
[ HORNS HONKING ]
Not this ! No !
Let go .
Manager Cho , this is all I have with me right now .
Sorry .
I 'll see you later .
[ HORNS CONTINUE HONKING ]
[ ♪ ]
Hey , Gang-du .
GANG-DU : Hyun-seo . It 's your Dad .
Hyun-seo !
Park Hyun-seo !
NAM-IL : Hyun-seo !
NAM-JOO : Hyun-seo !
Hyun-seo !
Why does he have to do that ? He 's not a kid .
Let him be . He wants to disinfect himself .
He 's worried he 'll pass the virus on to Hyun-seo .
Virus ...
All of us are fine ,
why do they keep going on about a fucking virus ?
If the government says so , we have to accept it .
What can we do ?
Is it the virus that 's making me so sleepy ?
Hyun-seo .
Look on the ground for footprints .
Hey , did Hyun-seo describe any special traits of the sewer ?
Special traits ?
We need some kind of hint here .
Hyun-seo said it was a big sewer .
Look how big this is .
GRANDPA : Yes , it seems we 'll find something .
Yeah , sure !
Wandering blindly through the sewers .
We need to think of a better way .
Stop complaining !
Put your time into searching another sewer instead .
Hey , tortoise ! Just try to keep up .
Slow-ass bronze medalist .
You wanna die ?
GRANDPA : Wait !
Hyun-seo ! Hyun-seo !
Turn it off !
Something moved there .
[ ♪ ]
It 's this way !
[ GUNS COCKING ]
Get down !
NAM-IL : What is this ?
It 's just water !
God damn it !
NAM-IL : How typical of you .
BOY : Sorry , Dad .
MAN : Did you pee ?
BOY : Because of the bangs , a little .
MAN : Why are they going around shooting ?
Wow , this cave really does lead to the Han River !
It 's not a cave , it 's a sewer .
They 're all connected like this .
Gosh , it 's hard to make a living .
Do we really have to go ?
So you 're not hungry ?
No , I 'm hungry .
If we do this once ,
we 'll eat well for a whole month .
Don 't you know that ?
I do .
Wow , there 's money too .
Don 't touch it .
Why not ? I 'm taking it .
If we take that too , it 's theft .
Put it back now , okay ?
We 're stealing from this place anyway .
Se-joo ...
This is not theft .
We 're now doing seo-ri .
Like melon seo-ri at a farm .
Hey , do you even know what seo-ri means ?
Seo-ri .
No ? The generation gap is pretty big .
It 's an old borrowing game kids play .
So seo-ri is a right of the hungry .
Run !
[ ♪ ]
[ CREATURE SNARLING ]
[ ALL SLURPING ]
[ CLEARING THROAT ]
[ CREATURE GROANING SOFTLY ]
[ CREATURE ROARS ]
[ ♪ ]
Hey .
What should I do ?
[ COUGHING ]
Are you okay ?
[ GROWLING ]
Look at that .
Isn 't that amazing ? In this situation ?
Wake him up , there 's no time .
GRANDPA : Let him sleep a minute .
He needs to sleep every so often .
Should we leave him here ? He 's no help anyway .
GRANDPA : Kids , wait a minute .
Sit down .
[ SIGHS ]
In your view ,
is Gang-du
really so pathetic ?
Yup . Yes .
You wouldn 't know it ,
but he was a really smart kid .
For example , when he was 2 ,
he 'd sit in front of the village store ,
and everyone walking by would ask him directions .
That 's how smart he looked .
As you know , when he was young ,
I was out of my mind ,
hardly ever coming home , staying out all night .
And this poor boy with no mother .
He must have been so hungry .
Going around , doing seo-ri all the time .
Raising himself on organic farms .
Whenever he got caught , he 'd get beaten up .
In this way ,
he lacked protein
when he needed it most .
So that 's why , every now and then ,
he dozes off like a sick rooster .
I think something up there ...
must have gone wrong too .
Have any of you heard it ?
The heartbreak of a parent who 's lost a child .
When a parent 's heart breaks ,
the sound can travel for miles .
So I really need to say this to you .
Be as nice to Gang-du as you can .
Don 't scold him , okay ?
Like last time ,
" Why 'd you grab another girl 's hand , moron ? "
You should never say things like that to him , okay ?
You know ?
I spend most of the day in the small food stand with him .
So whenever I hear him fart , I can tell right away
if he 's in B-minus or A-plus condition .
What do you two know ?
But even still , our Hyun-seo ...
Hyun-seo ?
Hey , you 're ...
It 's watching .
Huh ?
It 's watching us .
[ RAIN POURING ]
Fire !
[ SHOUTING ]
Fuck !
My head !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ CREATURE GROWLING ]
[ YELPS ]
Do you see it ?
What 's going on ?
Hyun - - Hyun-seo !
Hyun-seo !
GRANDPA : Quiet !
It 's moving .
What are you doing ? Make sure it 's dead !
No , wait !
Goddamn it ! That thing 's still alive ! ?
Don 't get too close !
Don 't !
Shoot it in the legs !
Just shoot !
[ GUNSHOT ]
There it is !
Shoot it in the tail !
The bullets ! No bullets !
[ GUNSHOTS ]
Hey !
My ears ! Stop it ! Are you trying to kill us ?
[ ♪ ]
Let 's go to the truck .
GRANDPA : Bring it on ! You all go on !
I 'm gonna finish that thing off !
Just run ! Anyone got any bullets ?
I 've got one left .
Good . Give it to me , and get to the truck .
Dad ! Come on !
Don 't worry about me , go to the truck !
Dad ! Just come here !
I 'll take you down with one shot this time .
Get up here !
Huh , what 's that ?
Nam-joo ! What are you doing ? Nam-joo !
When did she get there ?
Go back !
Nam-joo !
Oh , no !
Hey ! Somebody come get Nam-joo !
Stop playing around !
Hurry back ! Quick !
[ GUN CLICKS ]
[ GROWLING ]
GANG-DU : No ! Dad ! No !
Fuck ! No !
No !
Dad .
Dad , wake up .
Dad , the soldiers are coming .
Dad !
You two , get outta here ! Quick !
Fuck !
We should never have ...
Dad , what about Hyun-seo ?
Hyun-seo ! We can 't get caught . Hurry , hurry ! Run ! Run !
Dad !
What about Hyun-seo , Dad ?
[ ♪ ]
Dad !
Freeze !
Infected family located ! One captured , one dead .
Quickly !
Let 's begin . Hurry !
Cover him !
MAN : We have tragic news .
Sergeant Donald of the 8th U.S. Army ,
who through his act of courage
revealed to the world the existence of the virus ,
died today at 4 : 20pm .
As condolences flood in from all over the world ,
8th U.S. Army Commander Greenfield
held a rare press conference
to express his condolences .
WOMAN : Meanwhile the U.S. and WHO ,
citing the failure of the Korean government
to secure the remaining two infected family members
or to capture the creature in question ,
have announced a policy of direct intervention .
Yes , in this context , the unprecedented use
of " Agent Yellow " , is that correct ?
MAN : Yes , that 's correct .
Agent Yellow , which has been chosen for use here in Korea ,
is a state-of-the-art chemical and deployment system
recently developed by the U.S.
to fight virus outbreaks or biological terror .
This extremely powerful and effective system ,
once activated ,
completely annihilates all biological agents
within a radius of dozens of kilometers .
[ COUGHING ]
[ SHOUTING ]
WOMAN [ OVER SPEAKER ] : Indeed , we are trying
to provide Mr. Park the most pleasant environment
that a patient could want .
We are doing our best
to accommodate Mr. Park Gang-du .
[ ♪ ]
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
Hey ! When did you get here ?
Just a minute ago .
Nobody followed you , right ?
NAM-IL : It 's okay , I checked carefully .
And Nam-joo ? Where 's Nam-joo ?
Nam-joo ? Why ?
You travel separately , you two ?
So if you just type into the office 's computer ,
it shows up ? Really ?
Hyun-seo called late at night , right ?
Then the transmitter will be listed in the call records .
That means she 's within 200 meters of a transmitter .
That 's simple .
It 's that easy to get her location ?
That 's right , you should have come to me earlier .
Is all of your family so dumb all the time ?
[ SIGHS ] Right ...
All those sewers ... Fuck .
It 's okay , finding her is just a matter of time .
All thanks to you .
You were always busy protesting ,
when did you ever study ?
It must be really hard getting work at a telecom firm .
Still , I 'm just a salaryman .
But you must make 60 , 70 grand a year ?
My credit card debt is 60 , 70 grand .
Look .
Wait .
The time , the number ...
Here . This is it !
Are you sure ? Yeah .
Just a minute .
This is definitely her call .
Type this in .
ATR1020 .
It doesn 't work .
Really ?
The password , it must be in the manager 's room .
Here .
Hey , Nam-il ,
where is Nam-joo anyway ?
Why do you keep asking ?
She 's your sister , aren 't you worried ?
When we left the Han River ,
we just separated in the sewer .
I 'm sure she 's fine .
I see ...
Now what ?
It 'll be hard to get Nam-joo .
Seems like he really doesn 't know .
Then , let 's take care of Nam-il first .
He 's a real escape artist , though .
You should be careful .
Hey !
[ ♪ ]
By the way , how much is the tax on the reward money ?
Well , there 's an exemption ,
and there 's no tax on extra earnings .
I see .
Huh ? This ...
Hyun-seo !
Hey , it worked !
MAN : Mr. Park Nam-il , are you feeling sick ?
Greetings , Mr. Park . Just stay right there .
MAN : What are you doing ? Just come with us !
You should go to the hospital .
Fuck off !
[ SHOUTING ]
MAN 1 : What the - - ?
MAN 2 : Where is he ?
You rat ! Stop right there !
Hey ! Come on !
MAN 3 : Open this door !
MAN 4 : Hey ! Get him !
[ ♪ ]
[ PANTING ]
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
Shit !
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
Where is he ?
MAN 5 : Over there !
I don 't see anything !
Hey , Yong-bae , did you see him ?
MAN 6 : Let 's search the area .
[ PHONE BEEPING ]
[ BEEPING CONTINUES ]
[ TRAFFIC ROARING OVERHEAD ]
WOMAN [ OVER PHONE ] : There is no signal .
Please leave your message after the beep .
Nam-joo .
[ ♪ ]
[ WIND HOWLING ]
Hyun-seo !
WOMAN [ OVER PHONE ] : One new text message received .
[ ♪ ]
It 's me , Nam-joo .
Nam-joo !
I found it ! A huge sewer .
Right under the north side of Wonhyo Bridge !
I can 't reach Nam-il ! North side of Wonhyo Bridge ?
[ GRUNTING ]
GANG-DU [ OVER PHONE ] : Hello ? Nam-joo ! Nam-joo !
Are you okay ? Hello ?
Nam-joo ! Park Nam-joo !
Nam-joo !
Please calm down .
Wonhyo Bridge . Is it - - ? Where is ... ?
It 's near Yeouido , right ?
Yes , yes .
I need to go out for a minute .
Sit down . You need to get a shot .
What kind of shot did you say this was ?
An anesthetic .
Oh , right , right . I 'll get the shot before going .
Okay , let your arm relax .
But Wonhyo Bridge . Hyun-seo is still ...
MAN : Grab him !
Hyun-seo !
[ GRUNTING ]
GANG-DU : Let me go !
She 's near the north side of Wonhyo Bridge .
Is Wonhyo Bridge named after the monk Wonhyo ?
He wasn 't a monk . He was a priest .
Did you really inject the proper amount ?
Yes . For sure ?
We did for sure .
And it 's been an hour .
And he 's still like that ?
Yes .
Then what should we do ?
We should start the tissue sampling now .
[ YELLING ]
MAN : Why 's he like that ?
If we 've anaesthetized him , he should be sleeping .
Why 's he causing such a scene ?
Why ?
Excuse me , sir .
Don 't they use anesthetic here ?
[ GANG-DU SCREAMING LOUDLY ]
[ IN ENGLISH ] Oh , my god !
What 's going on here ?
[ IN ENGLISH ] Well , I guess they , um - -
No , no , no , no . No , no .
Stop this .
Now , Mr. Park .
I 've heard your daughter is still alive .
[ SPEAKING IN KOREAN ]
[ IN ENGLISH ] Is she really alive ?
Yes , he says his daughter is in a sewer
near Wonhyo Bridge .
Jesus !
Why didn 't you contact the police or the military ?
[ SPEAKING IN KOREAN ]
Because nobody - -
Haven 't you considered contacting a television station ,
or a human rights organization . Something ?
[ SPEAKING IN KOREAN ]
TRANSLATOR [ IN ENGLISH ] : Because nobody fucking listens to me .
Please don 't cut me off . My words are words too !
Why don 't you listen to my words ?
The virus has definitely invaded his brain ,
just as we suspected .
I agree .
It 's in the frontal lobe .
This man has no previous history of mental disorder ,
and yet he shows such strong symptoms of dementia .
[ IN KOREAN ] Let me go .
TRANSLATOR [ IN ENGLISH ] : But now he 's obviously completely delusional .
AMERICAN : This man 's brain is our last hope .
His brain ?
Yes . The virus must be in here .
It has got to be in here .
TRANSLATOR : Exactly what are you talking about ?
You don 't know about this ?
Now , this is strictly confidential .
Even among our team ,
very few know what I 'm gonna tell you .
My lips are sealed .
The late Sergeant Donald ,
the first one classified as a victim of the virus ,
was given an extensive autopsy ,
and no virus was found .
He died of shock during the operation .
Also , no traces of the virus
were found in any of the patients quarantined .
Simply put , so far ,
there is no virus whatsoever .
GANG-DU : Huh ?
[ IN ENGLISH ] No virus ?
[ IN KOREAN ] You mean there 's no virus ?
Right ? There 's no virus !
You 're talking about a virus that doesn 't exist .
Mister , they said there 's no virus .
So you should let me go now .
[ CRYING ]
My daughter Hyun-seo is under Wonhyo Bridge .
I need to go quickly . Please let me go .
Okay , mister , huh ?
[ YELLING ] You shitheads ! You bastards !
Please , mister , I beg you . Let me go .
I 'll give you my food stand , okay ?
I 'll give the rights to you .
What are you doing ? Please , mister ! Wait !
Fuck ! This is driving me crazy !
[ DRILL WHIRRING ]
I really need to get to Hyun-seo !
Mister , please save me ! What is this , please ?
[ CRYING ] Hyun-seo , I 'm sorry . Daddy ...
[ ♪ ]
Hyun-seo , you know what I want ? Banana milk .
Tell me what you want then .
Make a list of the top 10 things you want to eat
when we get out .
We have a food stand ,
so I 'll get you whatever you want .
Huh ? A stand ? I want to live there !
What about your home ?
I don 't have a home .
Really ?
No home , but a lot of homes .
And your mom and dad ?
I have a brother , but no brother .
Muscleman Sausage !
We got it !
Hard-boiled eggs !
Hot dogs !
Quail 's eggs !
Fried chicken !
Instant noodles !
Of course we do .
Then you must eat them every day ?
You know , kids from Chinese restaurants
don 't eat dumplings .
What do you want to eat most of all ?
Beer .
A cold beer .
BOTH : One , two , three !
Ya !
Uh !
Se-joo , you 've ridden piggyback before ?
Yeah .
[ CREATURE GROWLING ]
Another man 's coming out .
Please this time , a guy with a working cell phone .
[ CREATURE GARGLING ]
[ CLATTERING ]
[ BELCHING , RETCHING ]
[ HISSING ]
[ CREATURE GROWLING ]
[ THUMPING ]
[ SCREECHING LOUDLY ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Hey !
Dink !
[ ♪ ]
Everyone look here .
See this ? Get on the floor ! Move !
Hey , fat ass ! Get on the floor !
Get down . You like viruses ?
I 'll stick it right in your body .
You 're not lying down ? You want a virus bath ?
[ YELLING ]
You at the end ! Open the door , fast !
Open it !
You want to do it ? That 's right ! Open it !
Open it ! That one !
WOMAN : Open it !
GANG-DU : Open 'em all !
[ ♪ ]
Everybody get down ! You bastards !
Get down !
Where 's the car ?
You feasting out here ? Out of the way !
MAN 1 [ IN ENGLISH ] : Calm down , calm down !
[ IN KOREAN ] I 'm going to kill everyone !
Hey , start the engine !
If anyone follows , I 'll stick her full of virus !
Start the engine !
MAN 2 : Ambulance !
[ SHOUTING ]
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
[ MOANING ]
What are you doing ?
What ? Who are you ?
You punk ! After letting you sleep in my bed ?
Mister , where 's Wonhyo Bridge ?
Where do I have to go ?
Don 't have a cow . Do you even know where you are ?
I 'm in a real hurry !
How can I get to a main road ?
Figure it out yourself .
Mister , I need some soju bottles .
Wow , this is a nice bag .
Here , I 'll give you money .
Ah !
Think money can buy you anything ?
Well , I 'm bored anyway . Wonhyo Bridge ?
Okay , Wonhyo Bridge .
Jesus Christ .
What the hell ?
What are you two doing back there ?
Who uses those at demonstrations these days , you blockhead ?
I told you , it 's not for a demonstration .
Get out ! I 'll pull over , so get out !
Just keep driving . I 'm paying quadruple fare .
Quadruple ?
Wow , look at his hands work . He 's a master !
You said the north side of Wonhyo ?
That won 't be easy .
You see everyone heading in that direction ?
WOMAN [ OVER RADIO ] : Demonstrators are now gathering ...
It 's a total mess today .
... at the Agent Yellow release point .
The police have virtually given up
controlling the Han River restricted area ,
as demonstrators have broken past all barricades ...
[ ♪ ]
Hyun-seo !
[ COUGHING ]
Are you okay , Se-joo ?
I 'm hungry .
And blood keeps coming out .
It 's okay .
I 'm hot .
[ CREATURE GROANING SOFTLY ]
Se-joo .
Just stay right here .
Don 't come out , whatever happens .
Why ?
I 'll be right back .
I 'll bring
doctors ,
911 ,
the police ,
the military .
I 'll bring them all .
Take me with you .
[ ♪ ]
Se-joo .
Go in .
[ ♪ ]
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ CRYING ]
Hyun-seo !
[ SOBBING ]
[ CREATURE GROANING AND GROWLING ]
[ ♪ ]
Ah !
[ SHOUTING ]
Gang-du !
[ CREATURE , CROWD ROARING ]
[ SHOUTING AND CHANTING ]
Come on !
Hyun-seo !
It 's Daddy !
[ ♪ ]
WOMAN [ IN ENGLISH , OVER PA ] : Agent Yellow will be released in five minutes .
Please immediately evacuate
out of the 500 meter range of the release point .
[ ANNOUNCER SPEAKING IN KOREAN ]
[ IN ENGLISH ] Please keep walking
until you cannot hear this announcement .
[ ANNOUNCER SPEAKING IN KOREAN ]
[ CHANTING ]
What are you doing ?
Look .
[ YELLING ]
It 's here !
Everyone run !
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ IN ENGLISH ] Agent Yellow will be released in four minutes .
[ ANNOUNCER TALKING IN KOREAN ]
[ GUNFIRE ]
No , don 't shoot !
Don 't shoot !
Gang-du ! Hey !
Isn 't that Gang-du ? What the hell ? !
[ IN ENGLISH ] : Agent Yellow can be fatal especially to the elderly ,
children , pregnant woman ,
and those with respiratory disorders .
[ COUGHING ]
[ GROWLING , SNARLING ]
[ GUNFIRE ]
Don 't shoot ! Don 't shoot !
I said don 't shoot !
[ CREATURE SNARLING ]
[ ♪ ]
[ SOBBING ]
WOMAN [ IN ENGLISH , OVER PA ] : Agent Yellow can be fatal
especially to the elderly , children , pregnant women ,
and those with respiratory disorders .
[ SCREECHING FAINTLY ]
Yaah !
[ CREATURE SQUEALING ]
[ MEN SHOUTING ]
Gang-du !
[ ♪ ]
[ GLASS BREAKS ]
[ CREATURE SCREECHING ]
[ SCREECHES ]
[ GROANING ]
[ MOANING DEEPLY ]
[ ♪ ]
[ MUMBLING ]
Did you know Hyun-seo ?
Who are you ?
Were you with Hyun-seo ?
[ MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER TV ]
Let 's eat .
WOMAN [ IN KOREAN , OVER TV ] : A moment ago , at 11 : 30 p.m. ,
the U.S. Senate Investigating Committee
announced its findings
regarding the Korean virus incident .
Let 's go to the announcement .
MAN [ IN ENGLISH ] : The recent crisis in South Korea
occurred as the result of an error ...
There 's nothing good on .
... during the process of engaging ...
Should we watch something else ?
Let 's turn it off . Concentrate on eating !
Ultimately , the virus was not discovered
and we conclude that the cause of the crisis ...
Where 's the remote ?
... can and should be wholly attributed to misinformation .
[ WOMAN TRANSLATING IN KOREAN OVER TV ]
[ ♪ ]
[ CREATURE ROARING ]